Graduation day is right around the corner.
Can you believe it?
So, um, just wondering.
Why is your locker still so full?
Take your stuff home, girl.
Come on, I'll give you a hand.
Show me what you want to keep.
Okay.
But you're definitely throwing out those papers.
Too funny.
Is Hori your bestie or her mother?
Newsflash, you ain't packing so lightly yourself there.
Look who's talking.
You procrastinating pigs.
If you'd cleaned up a little every day, you'd be leaving like this.
Is that a free hand I see?
Two, if I'm not mistaken.
In that case.
What?
I swear, you guys.
We're putting your muscles to good use.
Holy crap, Hori.
You waited this late in the game to pack up shop?
No, these jerks just dropped their junk on me.
Hold on.
Speaking of stuff, where are your bags?
I planned ahead.
Put on my good boy pants and haul stuff back home every day.
Please don't look at me like that.
Hey, I have that same CD.
Good taste.
Actually, I think this one is yours.
I just forgot to return it.
My bad.
It's all cool.
Better late than never, right?
If you say so.
Come to think of it, I have some DVDs I borrowed off you.
Huh?
And she's not the only one.
There goes my easy commute home.
Farewell.
Zoe!
Are you?
Wow, you lightened your load, but you still have so much.
It would make way more sense if a bigger, stronger dude carried it for you.
Like me or Ishikawa or...
Hmm.
Ohori!
Oh, but why?
Oh, come on now.
It's not like he thinks of you as a dude.
He meant that people can rely on you, which is a compliment.
Hmm.
Oh, come on now.
Remy.
Would you mind taking care of the tra...
Ugh.
Yet another distraction.
Is that a travel magazine?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, a zoo feature.
What do you think?
Want to visit a big herd of giraffes?
I mean, who wouldn't, but...
Doesn't a day trip to the zoo sound fun?
We should all go.
Is it the same one we went to before?
Not quite.
Here, look.
Hmm.
That's a little more than a day trip.
I think it'd take at least two.
We'd also need a car.
And money for a hotel.
If we get a car and a hotel room, you guys will go?
You're making her think this might happen.
Do not get Remy's hopes up higher than they already are.
Okay, Mom.
In all honesty, though, I would really like a car.
It would literally open up avenues.
I can't wait to get my license.
If I had my own car, I could take you to way more places than just the zoo, you know?
We could go anywhere.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
You sure could.
I, um...
I can't help but wonder if this actually goes beyond visiting a zoo.
I'm not sure I follow.
Okay, so Remy's kind of thirsty.
Hold your horses there.
You can leave as soon as you tell us what's bothering you.
I'm fine.
So we're gonna do this the hard way, then?
Sengoku, if you would be so kind.
On it.
I promise you, there's nothing wrong.
I know you better than that.
Uh, Kono?
You have two choices.
Let us help you or show Yanagi something I doubt he's seen but won't soon forget.
Are you threatening her?
Remy's tough.
Do your worst.
Wait just a minute.
She's allowed to keep her thoughts to herself.
You don't need to resort to violence or whatever it is you're...
Oh, wow.
Her cheeks?
There's no point to this since we can't understand her and you want her to talk.
Sengoku, tell her.
It's a fairly rare face to see.
Take it all in while you can.
What?
Are you in any pain?
No.
It was like a massage.
It was?
So, here's the thing.
It's really not that big of a deal.
Remy just thought it might be nice to go someplace fun with everybody while we're still in high school since we're nearly done.
But then you guys started talking about cars and licenses.
And I realized all those things have potential to take you far away from me.
And I don't want that.
They also have the potential to help with running everyday errands.
That's true.
Anyway, we can nix the zoo idea.
Remy was just tossing it out there.
We don't need sporadic day trips to keep our friendship going.
Really?
You won't treat me like a stranger the second you graduate?
Of course not.
You aren't very easy to forget.
I know.
Huh?
As soon as I get my license, let's reconvene and plan a road trip.
I'm game.
We're two.
Oh, how about a beach?
Ah, you a fan of the sea breeze?
Oh, Remy likes the beach.
Let's swim.
I only want to look at the water, not swimming it.
Then after graduation, that's what we'll do.
We can make a pit stop at the zoo on the way there.
You could go all the time if you get a license as well.
But then who would ride shotgun?
Oh, I want a shotgun.
Maybe take turns?
Hori?
Earth to Hori.
She's down for the count.
Carrying everyone's stuff must have really taken its toll on her.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm here.
I guess she just wanted a pillow.
She's frowning in her sleep.
Well, that is one of her go-to faces.
Don't frown unless you actually want wrinkles on your forehead.
Eat, work, sleep.
That's all you do, huh?
You're so funny.
I hope days like these never end.
Even after high school.
Looking back, if that one single incident hadn't happened.
I mean, well...
If it hadn't happened.
Lise give us till the last day of school to turn in our graduation essays.
I forgot about that.
Speaking of graduation, I wonder what our picks look like.
Your guess is as good as mine, Hori.
All I remember was standing next to a guy I never even talked to.
Ishikawa!
You ready to bat?
Yeah.
And we still haven't spoken to this day.
But you're in the same class.
Oh, sorry.
It's fine.
You girls up for some bad singing?
Did your sister pass that exam?
Nah, she didn't.
Ugh, that majorly sucks.
Oh, I'm glad I ran into you.
Why's that?
Just came from the council room.
Ah, you finished cleaning?
Yes, it's Spick and Span.
Thanks, Gondo.
Sakura!
I'm ready to go when you are!
Hey, perfect timing, Remy.
She looked so much better when she had longer hair.
She's so unfriendly.
Walk faster, geez!
Get there when we get there, so stop rushing me.
Oh, before I forget, so about that shop you mentioned the other day.
Are you listening?
Do you know those boys?
Huh?
Oh.
No, I don't.
It's such a pain to take all my stuff home.
Ugh, it's such a pain to take all my stuff home.
I should have done it ages ago.
I should have done it ages ago, but I kept putting it off.
Attention students.
Please take the building at this time so the staff meeting may come up.
Yep, on my way.
Just one more week, and we'll be high school graduates.
I'm crossing my fingers that it gets a little warmer for graduation day.
I'm crossing fingers and toes.
OMG!
Did you see that guy?
He was like mega hot!
Wait, really?
He's a senior?
Oh, I wasn't paying attention.
Oh, wow.
Surprised somebody's still here.
I think I left my phone inside my desk.
And sure enough, there it is.
Hey.
This yours?
Huh?
Is what mine?
This silver thing.
Pretty sure I saw you drop it just now.
It looks like an earring.
Um, bye.
Hey!
What the hell?
What a weirdo.
I'm not entirely sure why.
But, ultimately, somehow.
Somehow.
My high school days amounted to nothing.
At least, that's how it feels.
People always wonder what if.
But dwelling on what could have been is pointless.
Although, you didn't have to wonder.
Mm-hmm.
Miyamura?
I'm sorry.
I was spacing out.
You okay?
What's going on inside that adorable little head of yours?
Hmm.
Just thinking.
There are so many different roads that led me to where I am today.
I could have easily taken another route.
And wound up somewhere else.
You know what?
I think we're exactly where we're meant to be.
We're together like this because that's how fate wanted it.
Maybe you're right.
There was a possibility of living in a world without you.
But that world's not my reality.
You're here.
Along with everyone else.
I'm not alone anymore.
Fate, he said.
I wonder if such a thing actually was responsible for bringing us together.
Even if this fate doesn't really exist,
I think the universe would have slowly, but surely,
moved me to the place I wanted to be.
Next on the docket, we will have the farewell address from this year's valedictorian,
Kakaru Sengoku.
Thank you, ma'am.
Nice one, he's me.
That big dummy!
Spring is finally spring, and with it we have blossomed and come into our own as the 63rd class of Catecurity High School.
All graduating students, please return to your-
Little punk!
You ruined everything!
Sorry about that!
It was a complete accident, though!
Yo, Miyamura!
Nice sneeze, dude!
That wasn't nice!
There's your sense of humor, brud!
Excuse me, Ishikawa!
No, I lost him!
Come on, man.
You're our valedictorian.
Should you really be tearing through the hallway?
Though you sure tore it up with that hype speech!
So, why were you chasing Miyamoto in the first place?
Did you miss the beginning of my speech?
I've got to apologize to him later.
It's a beautiful day.
And I see you're enjoying it.
Mm-hmm.
You chopped all your hair off.
Word spread about my piercings.
And tats.
I've got friends now.
Plus, a really great girl.
I got used to you completely ignoring me, but today you finally looked.
Yeah.
And...
I'll acknowledge you from now on.
Guess this is goodbye.
Congratulations.
You made it through.
Ah, there you are.
Come back down.
They want to get a group photo with everyone.
I know it's gorgeous out, but...
Uh...
Is something wrong?
No.
The wind's pretty strong today.
Teenagers.
Not even half the class is here.
Let's get a shot together while we wait!
Mind if I'm in it, too?
Well, fine.
Now say cheese.
Hey, the guys are graduating, too.
Take pictures of us, huh?
Why'd I devote any of my memory card to you fools?
Y'all wasted more than enough space in my brain as it is.
Come on, Yasuda!
Some of us would like to document this pivotal moment in our lives!
Party senpai!
I'm so sad I won't get to see you anymore!
What's up?
Well, you could always come over to my house.
Are you for real?
Not too often, though.
They're having one last hug.
Nice of you to indulge her for today.
It's the homestretch now.
Um, have you seen Remy around recently?
Oh, yeah, I think she was...
Wait, that was someone else.
Oh.
Hey, so...
I, uh...
Well...
Sorry for the words, right?
Thank you.
It's been a blast.
I really mean it.
My senior year was the highlight of my life,
and part of that was because of you.
I like both you and Yoshikawa so much.
You're my friends.
And I'll never forget you.
Me, too.
I won't forget.
I see.
That's good to know.
Thanks again.
Anytime.
And thank you.
Bye for now.
Take care.
See you around.
Sure will.
Well...
Guess it's best to leave all our high school baggage behind.
Goodbye.
Oh, hi!
Congrats on a job well done!
You graduated, too, so congrats yourself!
I suppose I did, huh?
Ah, that's right.
I have something extremely important to tell you.
Wow, this sounds major.
In the near future, I'd like to go somewhere with everyone.
As a group?
Right.
The other day, I got to talking with the student council crew,
and it made me realize something.
Once I can legally drive, I'd like to take a trip with my friends.
Friends.
The same as always.
Then there's Hori.
Kono sounded intrigued.
Sure!
Sounds great, so count me in!
I certainly will.
Just wear your glasses.
Huh?
It's unavoidable for some things to change once we graduate.
But I know without a doubt the friends I have today will be the friends I have tomorrow.
Hey!
There's my special little boy!
Hello, Kyosuke.
Whoa, is that Miyamura's dad?
He's so young.
I do see the resemblance.
What resemblance is that?
Come take a picture to preserve this lovely moment we're having, yeah?
Okay.
Let me go find one real quick.
Why in the hell would you go someplace you're not even welcome, you poor excuse for a father?
I thought it would be a good chance to have some time fun.
Damn it!
What kind of grown-ass man can't pull off a student's high?
Surely you'd like to meet up with your own parents, right, Miyamura?
My folks stopped by for a bit.
They had to hurry and get back to work.
Aw, don't get mad, honey bun.
You want me to be happy?
Then shut up and get lost!
Okay, I'm calling for a truce.
There, got it.
Yura, you're too much.
I think that I'm seriously...
Just too.
Moto, what a surprise.
Hi.
I take it this is your little sister?
That's right.
You come all this way to pick up your brother?
I'm here because Mom wanted me to let you know you have to come home early today.
Plus, I figured I could see what my new school would be like.
Oh wow!
You don't stay!
If that ceremony wasn't so darn long, I'd be home now!
But no time like the present, so let's get our butts and gear and book it, sis!
Guess I'll see you when I see you!
Okay, bye!
Bye!
You didn't lose any pep through all three years.
The song was right with the world.
Question for you.
Go ahead and ask me.
You're really my brother, right?
Better believe it.
Miyamura!
We're getting sushi to celebrate!
You wanna come?
Oh yeah!
Sweet!
Let's get going then!
Kyosuke's gonna be so excited to see you there.
Maybe too excited.
To the sushi!
There's no distance.
I've never been this close to someone before.
In my life.
Boundaries don't apply to us.
And I used to be terrified of that.
It shook me to my core, Hori.
But you know, because of you,
I felt a whirlwind of emotions I wasn't even aware I could feel.
I don't think either of us realized how nerve-wracking
simply being yourself around other people could be.
No fronts.
Just us.
Gradually breaking down our walls.
But you made me realize that and then some.
And I find myself asking,
what can I do for you?
How many ways can I make you smile?
You're one of the strongest people I know.
Yet still so fragile.
So delicate.
So precious.
Instead of a shadow,
bright sunny days are what follow behind you.
My whole life,
the only person I knew this well
was myself.
I was oblivious to how breathtaking the world could truly be.
And you came in and shattered my reality.
Thank you.
You told me you wanted a future with me.
But what can I do for you?
How can I repay you for what you've done?
Hurry up!
Mia Moura!
Wow.
The spring sky is bluer than I've ever seen.
If I could give you this very sky as a gift,
I would in a heartbeat.
And again.
Nah.
I know what you'd like.
A cake with tons of whipped cream on top.
That's more your style.
Bye.
Thank you.